Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
TYPHOON FAMILY
Break!
That was absolutely amazing!
Please give them
another big round of applause!
That was amazing!
I once asked Nam-mo
what was most precious to him.
Soldiers, even as we speak right now,
there is someone
who spends her nights up thinking of you.
It's none other than your mothers.
Back then, he chuckled,
asking why I asked him that question.
The forever refuge of our hearts.
Let us call on her.
-Mother!
Here she is.
Thank you for coming today, ma'am.
Nice to meet you.
-Why, hello.
-Yes, hello.
You must've brought
lots of delicious food.
No, I didn't go through much trouble.
I just bought everything my son likes.
-Is that so?
-Yes.
Ma'am, can you brag
about how great your son is?
My son has very long limbs,
and he's good-looking.
He also has a melancholic look
in his eyes, which isn't a bad addition.
He's good-looking.
She can't seem to stop laughing
at the thought of meeting her son soon.
-Right?
-Yes.
If any of you think
this lady is your mother,
come up on the stage.
Private Wang Nam-mo, sir!
Corporal Bae Song-jung!
I am sure she is my mother!
Do you have a reason for that?
Look at my long limbs
and melancholic eyes.
She has to be my mother!
What about you?
I already know
the lady back there is not my mother!
Then why are you here?
I wanted to say something
to my girlfriend.
Young-in, you're free
to go on dates for now.
But let us reunite after 19 months!
-Say it!
-Goodness.
Now, why are you here?
My mother cannot cook!
I always made her breakfast
even before I was enlisted!
If she chose to buy takeout food
even on a day like this,
I am perfectly sure that she is my mother!
So, whose mother is she?
Let us all call her out here together.
-Mother!
Here she is.
Please give her a big hand.
Do you see your son up here?
Have you met your son?
-Nam-mo.
-Her son's here!
Goodness, ma'am.
-Oh, dear.
-Oh, my.
His legs must've given out
because he was too nervous.
Are you all right?
Did you gain weight? Why are you so heavy?
-Good grief, you punk.
-Ma'am, please.
Oh, my. What do I do now?
-You're with your son now.
-I'm sorry.
Salute! I am Private Wang Nam-mo, ma'am!
Mother, please receive my bow!
Her son is giving her a deep bow.
Look at how brave he is.
He's a proud soldier of the ROK.
He's such a gallant soldier.
Ma'am, why don't you give him
the biggest hug?
Nam-mo.
Nam-mo…
But he didn't have to tell me
what was most precious to him.
And now, it's time to return home!
-Mom!
-Back then, it was such an easy question.
Thank you!
But now…
Although it's one-sided.
It's my first unrequited love.
-Unrequited love?
-Yes, unrequited love.
My unrequited love for you starts today.
What should I do?
Do you think I'll do a good job?
Do whatever you want.
You don't have to ask me.
Wait for me, my dear unrequited love,
Ms. Oh Mi-seon.
-What makes you so confident?
-Because it's an unrequited love.
Be careful. Behind you.
If someone asked me
what is most precious to me now,
how should I answer that question?
EPISODE 12:
MY REASON FOR LIVING
It's kind of off.
No, this won't work. It's too high.
Wang Nam-mo!
Hey, Mom. When did you get here?
That darned guitar. I'd better…
Tae-poong's company went under,
but he's still the CEO.
Good grief!
-Clean up everything.
-Have you eaten?
-Do you want ramyeon?
-No, I don't want to eat.
My goodness. This place is messy.
What on earth is this?
THE CUSTOMER'S HAPPINESS IS OUR PRIDE
I'm leaving first. Goodbye.
-Bye.
-Okay, bye.
-Look at that girl.
She's going to get a stomachache.
Nam-mo.
Are you still writing music?
It's just a hobby.
Who's this girl?
What do you think?
She's your son's girlfriend.
-Your…
-Isn't she pretty?
Don't fall for girls
just for their looks, please.
Think about what really matters, you punk.
You both look equally pretty.
Good grief. You fool!
I can't deal with this anymore.
-Get rid of these.
-What's wrong, Mom?
-Throw these away.
-What do you mean?
-I'll rip this out!
-No!
Are you all right?
Why did you suddenly come
and make a scene?
-Are you hurt?
-Cut it out. I'm fine.
It's okay to date just anyone for now.
But you should be serious
when it comes to marriage, got it?
Mom.
-What do you mean, "just anyone"?
-That girl…
What do her parents do?
Which school did she graduate from?
Where does she live?
She's just anyone if you don't know that!
Mom, I also don't have a dad
if you say it like that.
I barely got into a university,
and our family is penniless too!
Isn't that so?
You fool!
How dare you…
How dare you talk like that to me?
Just go, Mom.
Go home. I'm sleeping here tonight.
Do whatever you want.
And you…
You better act wisely around that sly girl
named Oh Mi-ho or whatever.
How does she know her name?
Ma'am, it's still hot.
So blow on it first.
Goodness, you're too kind.
-I appreciate it.
-Don't mention it.
It looks good.
Hey, Beom.
Wake up already.
Do you know what time it is?
Goodness, you're a mess.
Open your eyes, Beom.
Stay alert and watch out for cars.
-Okay.
-Have a great day!
Tae-poong! Time to go to work!
-I'm leaving!
-Okay, goodbye!
Grandma, eat slowly.
Okay? You have to chew well
and eat slowly.
Okay.
What's with him this early?
-I'm leaving, Grandma.
-Bye.
I'm going to work.
Little Ms. Oh.
Are you busy this week?
Well, take a look at this.
What?
What's this?
It's a notice from the Green Mothers' Club
for moms to stand in front of the school
with a flag for traffic control.
I could always fill in,
but I thought it'd be better
if his pretty sister showed up.
Why did he fold it like this?
He's that thoughtful.
Okay.
I'm leaving.
Have a great day.
-Can we have six sandwiches to go?
-Sure.
-We'll eat two here.
-Okay.
It's better when it's hot.
All done.
Here.
-Thank you.
-You got it on your hand.
Thank you.
I'm fine.
-Thank you.
-It's hot.
-Is it?
One second. We'll take a milk.
-Go ahead.
-No, I'm fine.
You must enjoy my sandwich a lot.
Isn't she adorable when she eats?
I like her.
Thank you.
It was good, wasn't it?
-Mr. Kang.
-Yes?
We're at work now.
You need to stop doing that.
Stop doing what?
That.
Your unrequited love.
Separating work from my feelings.
What a shame.
-Okay?
-Yes, ma'am!
-Thank you.
-Sure.
Wait.
Why are we the only ones eating?
What about you two?
-We already had one on our way here.
-Is that so?
Why didn't you have it with us?
-Because of my love.
-What?
-My love for a hot sandwich.
-Yes.
-I see.
-Enjoy.
Thank you.
I also have love…
for sandwiches loaded with sugar.
I'm disappointed, Ms. Oh.
You missed my preference today.
Sure.
Things seem slow here.
You're all having some sandwich.
Is it good?
The surgical gloves aren't manufactured
in three different places.
There's only one place in America.
That's monopoly.
So, who will benefit from this?
Those punks had bottles
of expensive liquor,
then gave us no discount.
They have a good reason not to, actually.
Blaze Eagles are monopolizing
the powdered gloves industry right now.
Monopolizing?
All right.
They're the only ones we can turn to.
Typhoon Trading has probably realized
they're bust, right?
They probably know they're bust.
-Hey, get over here.
-Yes?
PURCHASE SPECIFICATION
We received an estimate,
and their price is fixed,
regardless of quantity or conditions.
They hold a monopoly
and face no competition,
so there's no reason to negotiate.
This is a serious problem.
If the cost price is the same,
it's clearly an advantage
to Pyo Merchant Marine.
Why? Because they have a vessel?
Not just that. They have a warehouse too.
Those two already cost a fortune.
They may have a ship,
but it comes with an operation cost.
Why don't you run the numbers
with our profit margin at three percent?
We'll only make 9.18 million won.
Goodness, that's too low.
Are there any other costs we can cut?
We can cut on the warehouse cost
if we schedule everything perfectly.
The risk is too high for that plan.
Even the sea routes gets jammed sometimes.
-Where's the factory? In America?
-Malaysia.
Can we talk for a moment?
-Why? What do you want?
-We have something to discuss.
Don't mind us and carry on.
This is my area.
You should knock before you enter.
Are you two really friends?
We'll leave soon.
Do you have to do this, Mr. Kang?
-Pardon? But--
-I know.
We all worked very hard on this,
and we don't have
an alternative right now.
However, this is already a finished game.
It was your first time bidding,
and bidding is all about money.
The starting line
is basically different for us and them.
We're already seven to eight percent
behind Pyo Merchant Marine
in logistical costs.
Forget about the three percent.
This kind of gap is difficult to make up
even if we sell it without profit.
Are you saying we should give up?
That's your decision to make as the CEO.
Let's say we got lucky
and somehow landed the deal
without any profit margin.
Then what? We have to sign the contract
and pay the security deposit.
What will you use to pay that amount?
You know where that money is from.
I do. It's what we got
after moving out of our previous office.
Think wisely with both your heart and head
to make a sound decision.
It must be a burden.
But I guess that's the weight
you must carry as the CEO.
The weight of five people
who depend on you to make our living.
Hey, Tae-poong. I'm against that.
You won't give up until the end, will you?
That's the attitude that suits you.
SHIPMENT, DEPARTURE, ARRIVAL,
DELIVERY, STORAGE, BID PRICE
Is there really no way around this?
We're at different starting lines.
The starting lines.
-Hey.
-The starting…
You're still here?
Yes, I had to think about something.
Thinking is a wonderful thing.
Have I run out already?
I thought I had enough.
I always had this at wholesale price,
so it feels too expensive
to buy it out there.
-Is there a huge difference?
-Quite a bit, actually.
What about chicken?
Does that come at a wholesale price?
Yes, there's a business
that delivers only raw chicken.
That's where we get it.
You know, we still used
high-quality chickens here.
By any chance…
By any chance, do you know a way to get it
even cheaper than the wholesale price?
Would I sit around like a bum if I knew?
How would you do that?
Go to the farm and slaughter chickens?
The farm?
TYPHOON TRADING
PYO MERCHANT MARINE
If we have different starting lines,
why don't we pull up one more step?
Here's what I mean.
Instead of the headquarters in America,
let's go straight
to the factory in Malaysia.
FACTORY - COST
Then, we'll get it at a cheaper price.
Would Blaze Eagles let this slide?
It's all right.
That's not the only client they work with.
That's a relief. We might have a chance.
Should I find out
the factory's phone number?
No, it'd be better
to go in person instead of calling.
The bidding is in two days,
and you should be there, Mr. Kang.
Of course, someone else
will have to go to Malaysia.
Please?
You want to swap shifts with me?
Are you going somewhere?
-I have to go to my brother's school.
-That little boy?
I already have plans.
-Please? Just this once.
-Jeez.
All right.
It's my turn next, okay?
Really? Thank you so much.
I'll treat you twice next time.
Go, now.
Thank you. I'm leaving!
Does she not have family?
She lives with her grandma,
but she has dementia.
Dementia?
Once her older sister gets married,
her grandma and younger brother
will be her responsibility.
That poor girl.
-Have a great day.
-All right. Thanks, bye.
Goodness.
Oh, my. Does this even cover anything?
It looks more like a mask.
Jeez.
-Nam-mo.
-Yes?
What do you think?
Let's see.
This doesn't look like your style, Mi-ho.
How do I put this? It's for older…
-No, it's a mature style.
-Really?
Will I look like his mom?
Excuse me. Coming through.
Nam…
My back hurts.
-Nam-mo.
-Yes?
-Is that all she has to wear?
-Mi-ho.
I love it when you do that.
-But I'm gross and sweaty now.
-No, not at all.
She's wiping sweat with her hand?
-You're so wet!
-Doesn't she have a handkerchief?
Great, I'm all recharged now. One moment.
My gosh.
Now, where am I headed next?
The next stop? Let me help you.
All right.
Wow! Made in America.
Awesome.
I even love the popping sound.
-American juice surely is good.
-It is good. Yes.
Mr. Pyo still believes all these
are on their way to the PPS.
We need to make space for the gloves.
-Just pull them out.
-Yes, sir.
And we can always sell these somewhere.
My friend is the son
of Center Department Store's CEO.
-Reach out to them.
-Yes, sir.
Okay, we're all done here.
Did you run the numbers on our bid?
Yes, I ran the numbers
with our bidding price
at a profit margin of 12%.
-At 12%?
-Yes, sir.
Jeez.
That sounds too high.
-Did you want to make money with this?
-No, sir.
Mr. Pyo, we already have the upper hand
because of the logistics costs,
and we need this profit
to run the business--
Stop racking your brains
and drop the price.
Let's play it safe.
It is good.
-Mr. Ha!
-Yes, sir! I just gave it a taste.
MALAYSIA
I'll get it.
Hello, you've reached Typhoon Trading.
-It's me.
-It's Mr. Bae!
Hey, put him on speaker.
Hello? Can you hear me?
Yes, we can. Did you arrive?
What?
No, I haven't eaten anything yet.
Did you hurt your ears?
Did you get into an accident?
That's not what's important.
I came, and there's huge trouble.
The factories have changed.
What? The factories have changed?
Yes, the head office
called off the contract,
so this factory now makes pillows.
It's three for 10,000 won.
-Pillows? Like for sleeping?
-What about the gloves?
They don't make the gloves here.
It's now made on another island,
but this country
has well over 800 islands.
But tomorrow's the bidding.
It's on another island?
When was the contract canceled
at that factory?
I heard it was quite recent,
but I don't have a way of finding out…
-Hello?
Can you hear me? Hello?
-Mr. Bae!
-It was cut off.
-It got cut off.
-You can't get him back now.
It took so many tries to get through!
CHANGJEON ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
-Oh, wow.
-Look.
-Whose mom is that? She's really pretty.
-What are you talking about?
PLEASE STOP AT THE LINE
She's my sister.
She's my sister
who's much better than any mom.
GREEN MOTHERS' CLUB
Hey, wait for me!
CHEONHO-DONG TO JONGNO 1-GA
"PLAINS OF HOPE" BIDDING DAY
Has Mr. Bae reached out?
He called, but the call
keeps getting disconnected.
There was something I asked him to do,
but it's not easy to reach him.
What can we do now?
We have to go.
Otherwise, we'll lose the bid bond.
Yes, we'll go and bid at a very high price
or do our best and lose heroically.
Let's go there for now and wait.
I know he'll do
whatever it takes to reach out to us.
MOMO'S PUB
SEOUL OFFICE
OF THE PUBLIC PROCUREMENT SERVICE
WE WILL SUPPORT
NEW SMES' ENTRY INTO THE MARKET
Keep it up.
Drop the shoulders.
-Looking great.
-Good.
You're good. You're loosening up.
Excellent. Great posture.
-You're all good.
-You're good.
Try not to move your wrist.
Don't let anyone guess
what you're writing. Make it discreet.
-Okay.
-Good.
-Where there's a will, there's a way.
-What now?
Where there's a will, there's a way.
-Okay. All right.
-Okay.
We cannot have any problems from A to Z.
-All right?
-Impressive. You have grown.
Mr. Kang.
-Yes!
Mr. Kang, take a look at this.
If you get confused, choose one from here.
I ran the numbers
from 5% profit margin to 15%.
Hey, Ms. Oh, this is even more confusing.
Mr. Kang, let me share my secret with you.
KANG TAE-POONG
One, two, three, four. One, two…
Thirteen.
Okay, this is it.
Go with this number.
-You want me to take the fifth option, 9%?
-Yes.
-Bid that number.
-Are you serious?
Mr. Koo.
If you keep this up,
you'll end up in hell.
That paper has been blessed.
What a bunch of bums.
You all are such a joke.
Are you trying to be
the terrifying underdogs?
You look way too serious.
Hey, Freckles.
You're the female lead.
-Don't look that way.
-What's going on here?
This isn't a flea market.
Is the entire staff
of Typhoon Trading here?
Good grief!
I want to see only two here,
just like them.
The rest can wait outside.
He hasn't called, right?
Buy some time.
Stall for time.
Excuse me. I have a question.
Do you have a policy of keeping only two?
I haven't seen it. Why two?
Could you tell me the reason?
-I don't see it.
-It's not in here.
Why should only two remain?
-There's no rule.
-Right?
Get out of here. Now!
You have to tell me why.
I can't leave without a reason.
My goodness. She's so stubborn.
This is killing me.
She just told you to leave!
We need more time.
-Where is that rule? Two people?
-I don't see it.
-I have to pray now.
What? You have to pray!
I'm sorry to ask,
but I must be here alone.
-May I have some privacy?
-Hey, look.
-He has to pray to live.
-He does.
Hey, you can't do this!
-This guy?
-Get them out of here.
He's a Buddhist.
-One second.
-He has to pray right now.
He has to pray now.
Mister!
Get him out of here!
-When we're upset
What's he doing?
-He's not done.
-No.
-You can't do this here!
-Stop bothering him!
You have to get up.
Get out.
-We have to start bidding.
-Bless you!
Follow your heart.
-You have to leave now!
-Why do we have to go?
-What is wrong with you?
-My gosh!
We'll begin now!
We will begin the bidding.
The bidding ends at 11:15 a.m.
BIDDER: PYO MERCHANT MARINE
AMOUNT: 433,444,043 WON
Yes, sir.
Hey, what are you doing?
Are you scared?
Let me give you a hint.
Try begging and say, "Please."
Please.
Hey, you need to start thinking
with some common sense.
You don't do business
by pulling petty tricks.
You do it with money.
But you have no money,
no warehouse, and no ship,
which makes you a loser
from the beginning.
-Let's go, Mr. Pyo.
-Okay.
All right.
You've lost.
Here.
And here.
Lastly, here.
Why is this so complicated?
Mr. Kang.
You need to start writing now. Do it.
We still have some time.
Just a little more.
-I'm sure he'll reach out.
-Okay.
Officer.
-A telegram came.
-A telegram?
-For me?
-No.
-Mr. Kang Tae-poong?
-Yes!
How important was that telegram
that it had to be sent here?
-A family event?
-Please leave.
Wait.
This is unfair.
There are only three minutes left.
Wait, it's…
It's very urgent.
-It's my father--
-He died, you punk.
His deeply beloved wife, my mother.
Goodness gracious. How important is this?
I'm getting curious. Read it.
Cut the crap. Open it now.
-Open it now!
-Right? I'll do that.
I wanted to open it. I'll do it.
TO KANG TAE-POONG,
SEOUL PUBLIC PROCUREMENT OFFICE
"Five, one, one, one, stop.
Four, zero, stop. Okay, stop."
What is this?
-Is this…
-It sounds like a code.
-Right?
-Is he a spy?
I know.
"Work five days a week,
every hour and minute for 40 years, okay?"
I don't think that's it.
It's about time you wrapped up everything.
We have a while…
Oh, no! We have a minute left.
You have a minute to make your bid.
Please hurry.
BIDDING APPLICATION
-I'm on my way.
-It must be sealed!
-Right.
-You have to seal it tightly first.
Sealing.
-Stay calm.
-Tightly.
Sealing tightly.
-Stay calm.
-Sealing.
-And I need your seal.
-Yes, of course.
-The seal. The inkpad.
-The inkpad.
Why the heck is she so strong?
Two.
-All right.
-Three.
We did it!
-Good work.
-Sure.
Great job.
The old geezers are here.
We'll sit here.
Now, the bidding has ended.
Let me announce the winning vendor.
The vendor that made the winning bid
for three million surgical gloves is…
The winner is
Typhoon Trading.
-All right!
-Yes!
-My gosh!
-We did it!
-Yes!
Cut the crap!
-That doesn't make any sense!
-See it for yourself then.
-We won
-See it for yourself.
-We got it!
-Hey, get that from him later.
-Yes, ma'am.
PYO MERCHANT MARINE: 433,444,043 WON
TYPHOON TRADING: 428,580,315 WON
This can't be.
Let me take that if you're done.
They couldn't have bid that price.
This is bad.
We won, so let's get out of here.
Let's go back to the office. Hold hands.
Let's leave quickly
before they raise an objection.
Let's go. I'll order tangsuyuk.
-Really?
-Yes.
Great work.
It's all thanks to Mr. Bae.
-So when was the contract canceled?
-They said it's been about ten days.
-Ten days?
That means they couldn't have removed
the gloves in stock.
Mr. Bae, do they have them in stock?
What? The stock?
They don't just have a little in stock.
There are over 5,000 boxes,
5,111 to be exact.
-Then let's take everything.
-Let's do that.
The problem is the price.
I don't know how much to offer.
-Well, you can go with--
-We have to lowball them.
Go for like 60%, maybe 70%.
-We shouldn't do that.
-How about 59%?
No, I think we should
take our time to negotiate.
Hello?
-Hello?
-Mr. Kang?
-Mr. Bae.
-Hello?
-Mr. Bae?
-Bae Song-jung?
-Where did he go? Hello?
Jeez.
That's going to get me in trouble.
TELEGRAM
"Five, one, one, one, stop.
Four, zero, stop. Okay, stop."
What is this?
They don't just have a little in stock.
There are over 5,000 boxes,
5,111 to be exact.
We got it!
STANDARD PURCHASE AGREEMENT
CONTRACTOR: TYPHOON TRADING
Are you that happy?
We can make a living now.
People might think
you've been starving all along.
Don't smile like that.
You're too pretty.
No, it's after hours,
so you can be pretty.
You know…
It's hard to separate work from feelings.
Jeez.
So, is Mr. Bae coming back tomorrow?
Yes.
Where did you get the idea
that the factory would have stocks left?
From three aspects of sales,
clients, revenue, and…
-Inventory.
-Precisely.
You know that well.
But you know, lowballing them was a bit…
-Was that awful?
-No, it was way too cool!
I knew it.
That's why
you're Typhoon Trading's trader.
Thank you.
-Sure.
-Thank you.
What's the most precious to you, Ms. Oh?
I don't know. I've never thought about it.
Well…
Rice and briquettes
are both very precious.
But you know,
to me, it's tomorrow.
-Tomorrow?
-Yes.
In the past, I could endure today
only by thinking that there's tomorrow.
But it's a bit different now.
When tomorrow comes,
I will have learned some more
and reflected a bit more,
so I could become
slightly better than I am today.
What about you?
What's the most precious to you?
Me?
To me…
The most precious thing is…
I can't tell you yet.
I'll tell you later.
Darn it.
This again. Jeez.
It's such a mess.
Thank you.
My dear Nam-mo must be looking for you.
Yes.
-Sorry?
-I am Nam-mo's mother.
And you better throw that away.
I was going to throw it away.
Hey, can we chat for a moment?
Well, may I buy you food somewhere?
When you address your elder,
use proper words like "treat" and "meal."
Okay.
And it's not going to be a long chat,
so let me make it quick right here.
I don't want you to date Nam-mo.
-Sorry?
-It must feel too sudden, right?
But I thought I should make
something like this loud and clear.
Nam-mo is a kid who always does as I say,
so I'll convince him the best I can.
So,
stop seeing each other
before it gets more serious, okay?
Let's do that.
Why?
What do you mean?
Why do you hate me?
No, it's not that I hate you.
It's different from hating you.
It's not hatred, but…
Gosh.
You are…
You're extremely poor, aren't you?
And your parents aren't with you.
Your grandmother has dementia,
and your brother is still very young.
I have an older sister too.
Right. I see.
But you know, once she gets married,
she's as good as a stranger.
When that happens, your remaining family
will become my son's responsibility.
He doesn't have the ability
to handle that kind of life.
When that happens,
I'll end up with the burden,
but I can't handle that either.
You know it, don't you?
Poverty…
is like a joint guarantee
without a contract.
That's why I'm scared of it.
I don't plan to give him my burden.
That…
is easier said than done.
Miss.
When I was younger than Nam-mo's age now,
I became a widow.
People around me pitied me
and treated me nicely
when they were with me.
But they were saying behind my back
I had bad luck.
It felt so unfair.
But what can I do?
That's how the world works.
Ms. Oh Mi-ho.
Since you and I are the unfortunate ones,
let's avoid each other.
Please.
Okay?
Mom.
How did you… Why are you here?
Hey, why are you crying?
-What did you say to her?
-I didn't say anything.
What did you just say?
I told her to stop seeing you.
You too, get a grip!
Your friend is a CEO
who wears a tie to work.
Will you continue to haul
those bags of clothes every night?
Is that Mi-ho's fault? Is it?
Why are you blaming someone else
for my incompetence?
Why are you blaming her
for our wrong life choices?
-What?
-It's true!
I had an impossible dream,
and you believed that total fraud's words.
Mom, we ended up like this
not because of the world or other people.
It's because we lived like fools!
Aren't I right?
You…
And you.
Are you going to break up with me?
No, let me make this clear first.
I don't care what my mom said.
I'm not leaving you, okay?
-Enough is enough, Wang Nam-mo!
-What's enough?
I don't plan to break up with Mi-ho,
so apologize to her right now!
You've lost your mind!
I am…
not sure anymore.
Mi-ho.
You're dating me, not my mom.
Let's go.
Wang Nam-mo!
If you take one more step,
I will never see you again.
Mom.
I'm paying rent for the store
thanks to Tae-poong,
and Tae-poong
is living off Mi-ho's family.
Mi-ho is the best off among us!
If anyone wants to break us up,
it should be her family!
Let go of me.
Let go.
What do you want?
Why are you mad?
You need to go.
I haven't decided
if I'll break up with you or not.
So, I don't want to see you. Get lost!
Hey, Mi-ho.
Why do you act tough when you're with me?
You should've said everything
you wanted earlier, just like now.
Why did you look like
you did something wrong?
Don't just stand there like a fool
when someone messes with you!
She's your mother!
Yes, I am extremely poor.
But I've never begged anyone for help.
I've never coveted what wasn't mine.
My grandma…
My grandma
raised me like that.
So, why would my sister be a stranger?
Why is my family a burden?
What's so great about your family?
I speak better English than you,
and I worked at the department store
longer than your mom.
So, how dare she talk and look down on me?
-What a weird woman.
-My mom said those things because--
I feel like a fool for not saying a word
just because she's your mom,
so you need to get lost, please.
One more thing.
My life isn't unfortunate.
I may not have parents,
but I have three in my family.
but I have my grandma,
Beom, and my sister,
whom I love very much.
I'm sorry, Mi-ho.
I'm so sorry
you had to hear that from her.
BELLUA DEPARTMENT STORE
Jeez! Enough!
You idiot.
I thought you had stopped causing trouble,
but you ended up with this mess?
I'm also as pissed off as you are.
-I'm much more irritated than you are!
-Irritated?
Your irritation doesn't matter.
Do you know how much the juice was?
It was $150,000!
How are you going to make up
over 200 million won of loss?
Dad.
-I have a plan too.
-What plan?
You couldn't possibly have a plan!
If the department store returns it,
that'll be the end!
You're…
I told Mr. Ha to remove your office.
-Get ready to go to America.
-America?
-And return the juice?
-Go there and study.
You're nothing right now.
You have such a long way to go.
-You can't do anything!
-Dad!
It's not over yet.
I may have taken a few jabs,
but one uppercut will end that punk.
Business isn't like boxing.
It doesn't matter
if you get beaten up and fall down.
-Whoever lasts longer in the ring wins!
-I don't care who lasts longer!
I'll land a big blow on him
and buy out the entire game.
What is it?
Why did you suddenly want to see me?
There's no business between us.
Hey, lady.
Darn it.
Who do you think would feel
more humiliated if we were seen together?
That's not what I mean.
This situation is ridiculous.
Why should I meet you?
You're a spy, right?
What are you talking about?
I can't believe
you stabbed Tae-poong in the back.
Stabbed him in the back?
-I haven't done anything like that yet.
-"Yet"?
That means you're planning to.
I saw something at my dad's desk.
It had your home address,
the names of your family,
and everything else written up there.
I wonder what he's going to do.
It's a shame.
I don't care
what that piece of paper says.
What do you want from me?
I'm sick and tired
of that promissory note!
Promissory note?
I see.
So, that was it?
Oh, no.
SAMGOK WAREHOUSE
Excuse me.
The gloves came earlier than expected.
I could've done the due diligence alone.
It'd be better if we do it together
and have it done faster.
I also get to see you.
There's the truck.
-Hello.
-This is the last one.
-Thank you.
-Goodbye.
-Bye.
-Let's go eat.
-Thank you.
Thanks for your hard work.
Enjoy your lunch!
Gosh.
-Everything is here now.
-Yes.
It'll take a while
to check all the quantities.
Then you must be hungry.
-I'll get us something to eat.
-I didn't see anything nearby.
No, there are a lot of food joints
just down the corner.
I'll get some in a flash.
-Okay, see you.
-Okay.
SURGICAL GLOVES INVENTORY
-My goodness.
-What happened?
Are you badly hurt?
I'm fine.
Really?
Something's making me uneasy.
But he said he wasn't traveling far today.
It's true.
The students were all drafted as soldiers.
I was worried sick
as I waited for my husband.
I can't imagine
what it's like to wait for your son.
My children are still young,
so I don't know what that's like.
You're right.
I don't feel at ease staying home
while pushing my son out to work.
Oh, dear.
All right.
Come here.
Let me see that.
Let me put this on like this.
Oh, dear.
All good.
You're done.
It must be hard to live in poverty
after living many years
of such a good life, isn't it?
But you never show it
to anybody under this roof.
I can tell that you're very kind.
Everything's going to work out, okay?
Ma'am…
All done.
What is that smell?
What?
No, wait.
Oh, my gosh!
No, this can't happen!
What do I do? But how?
How did a fire break out?
Wait. Let's see.
No, please.
Please stop.
No, this can't happen.
No, please.
No.
No!
NATIONWIDE
BIRTH OF THE G2 DIGITAL PCS!
Would Ms. Oh like that?
What do I do?
It's hot!
Please help!
This can't be happening.
No…
What do I do?
Jeez!
Ms. Oh!
Darn it.
Oh Mi-seon!
Hold on. Hang in there.
Please…
Ms. Oh!
Back then, Nam-mo also asked…
…what was most precious to me.
Oh Mi-seon!
If someone asked me the same question,
about what was most precious to me…
Mi-seon.
…I would say
it's you.
Hang in there.
Hold on.
Oh Mi-seon!
MY REASON FOR LIVING
TYPHOON FAMILY
And yet, the warehouse burst into flames.
Are we sure it wasn't arson?
From now on, I will never leave you alone.
You've had an accident
with only a week left until the deadline?
Tell me you're joking!
Did you go through the documents here?
I swear I had these arranged neatly.
I've got it.
I found out why Blaze Eagles
has a supply shortage.
Hyun-jun!
Even if I die,
Typhoon Trading won't go down.
Subtitle translation by: Eunsook Youn